var initFaw = () => globalThis.fawazir = new fawazirCls([
	{
		nb: 3,
		fawazir: [
			{
				question: 'hallo',
				values: [
					'ali',
					'world',
					'error'
				],
				correct: 0
			},{
				question: 'halloo',
				values: [
					'al',
					'world',
					'error',
					'ali'
				],
				correct: 3
			},{
				question: 'hall',
				values: [
					'world',
					'error',
					'ali'
				],
				correct: 2
			},{
				question: 'haallo',
				values: [
					'world',
					'error',
					'ali',
					'ali1'
				],
				correct: 2
			}
		]
	},{
		nb: 4,
		fawazir: [
			{
				question: 'hallo',
				values: [
					'ali',
					'worrld',
					'erroor'
				],
				correct: 0
			},{
				question: 'halloo',
				values: [
					'all',
					'world',
					'errrror',
					'ali'
				],
				correct: 3
			},{
				question: 'hall',
				values: [
					'wrld',
					'errr',
					'ali'
				],
				correct: 2
			},{
				question: 'hao',
				values: [
					'world',
					'ror',
					'ali',
					'al1'
				],
				correct: 2
			}
		]
	},{
		nb: 5,
		fawazir: [
			{
				question: 'haaaaallo',
				values: [
					'ali',
					'wold',
					'error'
				],
				correct: 0
			},{
				question: 'loo',
				values: [
					'all',
					'wod',
					'error',
					'ali'
				],
				correct: 3
			},{
				question: 'hll',
				values: [
					'wrld',
					'er',
					'ali'
				],
				correct: 2
			},{
				question: 'hao',
				values: [
					'wrld',
					'ror',
					'ali',
					'al'
				],
				correct: 2
			},{
				question: 'hall00o',
				values: [
					'ali',
					'worr00ld',
					'er0roor'
				],
				correct: 0
			},{
				question: 'hal11loo',
				values: [
					'al11l',
					'world',
					'errrror',
					'ali'
				],
				correct: 3
			},{
				question: 'hal2l',
				values: [
					'wrl123d',
					'er3rr',
					'ali'
				],
				correct: 2
			},{
				question: 'ha22o',
				values: [
					'wo2rld',
					'ror',
					'ali',
					'al1'
				],
				correct: 2
			}
		]
	}
])